epictimes.com 2016-11-07

# Privacy Policy - EpicTimes

Thank you for visiting Epictimes Inc website (the "Site")! The Site is strongly committed to protecting

your privacy. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform users of the Site as to what information we

collect and how and why we use such information.

 **Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information.**

Through the Site, including any mobile version thereof, users may enter personal information about

themselves. This policy explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you

can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand

this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. Please note that our online

information collection and use practices may differ from our practices regarding information obtained

offline.

REMEMBER: IF YOU MAKE USE OF THE SITE, REGISTER WITH THE SITE, REQUEST

INFORMATION THAT WE MAY OFFER, OR SUBMIT INFORMATION IN ANY WAY TO OR

THROUGH THE SITE YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS. AS WE UPDATE AND EXPAND OUR

SERVICES, THIS POLICY MIGHT CHANGE, SO PLEASE REVIEW IT FROM TIME TO TIME.

 **The Information We Collect.**

We may collect information about you through a variety of methods, such as your participation in games,

quizzes, contests, chat rooms, forums or the like or other documents that you submit to us, transactions in

which you may engage with us or our affiliated companies ("Affiliates"), or through visits that you may

make to the Site, including via our mobile applications. This policy applies to all personally identifiable

information that we collect and maintain about our users in connection with providing services, such as:

• Your contact information (such as name, Twitter handle, postal and email address, or phone

number);

• Username and password for the account you may establish on our sites;

• Demographic information (such as age, date of birth and gender);

• Location information, such as the real-time geographic location of the device on which you install

our mobile applications; and

• Other details that you may submit to us or that may be included in the information provided to us

by third parties.

• Your credit card information for purchases and/or subscriptions

You may view or change your information at any time by [contacting us](http://www.epictimes.com/contact/).

You also can engage with our content, such as video, games, applications, and other offerings, on or

through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook or third-party social media plug-ins and

applications. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-  
ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile

(e.g., your name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, list of friends, people you follow and/

or who follow you, the posts or the 'likes' you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of

the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, games

played and performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have

been shown or may have clicked on,) from your interaction with our content.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things

like: (i) give you exclusive content; (ii) personalize your online experience with us within and outside

our applications or websites; and (iii) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by

sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By doing so, you consent to the use of this

information in accordance with our privacy policy. When you provide personal information to us through

an application, on our sites, or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of

these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

Through some social networking sites' privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more

information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their

respective privacy policies and terms of use.

 **Other Collected Information**

We also may use third-party website analytics tools (such as Omniture or Google), that collect information

about visitor traffic on our sites and mobile applications. The information we may collect by automated

means includes:

• Information about the devices our visitors use to access the Internet (such as the IP address and the

device, browser and operating system type);

• URLs that refer visitors to the Site;

• Dates and times of visits to the Site;

• Information on actions taken on the Site (such as page views and site navigation patterns)

• A general geographic location (such as country and city) from which a visitor accesses our Site;

and

• Search terms that visitors use to reach the Site.

 **When you use our mobile applications on your mobile device, you may choose not to share your**

 **geo-location details with us by adjusting the device's location services settings. For instructions on**

 **changing the relevant settings, please contact your service provider or device manufacturer.**

 **How We Use Your Personal Information.**

We use your personal information to provide you with products or services that you have requested, to

respond to questions or communications and to get in touch with you when necessary. For example, we

may use your personal information to communicate with you or to send you information that you have

requested. Additionally, by registering for the Site you will be automatically entered into sweepstakes and

contests held on the Site. Except as otherwise set forth on the Site, in addition, we may send to you an e-  
mail offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to ask you to participate in a

survey.

 **Updating or Removing Your Personal Information.**

Please [contact us](http://www.epictimes.com/contact/) at any time to update or change your personal information.

 **How We Share Your Personal Information.**

We will not share with third parties the personal information you provide except (a) if it is for the

purpose(s) you provided it; (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary

to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to

a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury

to or interference with the rights or property of another); (d) with other persons, service providers or

companies with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business

activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the Site);

and/or (e) notifying you when we make material changes to one of our subscriber agreements or this policy.

Examples of us sharing your personal information for the purposes submitted are if you participate in a

third-party survey or request information from a third-party, we may provide the information provided to

such third party so that they can send to you directly the information you requested. We will seek to obtain

your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an "opt-in" or "opt-out" method,

or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail). However, if we pass on personal information to an

Affiliate, we require that it protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. If you

want us to stop sharing your personal information among Epictimes Affiliates, please [contact us](http://www.epictimes.com/contact/).

Additionally, with your consent, we may share the personal information you provide online with companies

not affiliated with us (i.e. third party companies) who are interested in marketing their products or services

to you or in asking you questions, both online and offline. We will seek to obtain your consent either by an

"opt-in" or "opt-out" method, or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail). Companies with whom

we might share your personal information may include consumer products, telecom, financial, military,

market research, entertainment, and educational services companies and their third party service providers.

If you want us to stop sharing your personal information with these companies, please [contact us](http://www.epictimes.com/contact/). If you

consent to receiving communications from non-affiliated companies, you may need to communicate with

them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications or if you wish

to change any data you provided online. In this instance, any changes or amendments to your personal

information must be given directly to each company who communicates with you as these changes,

amendments and/or deletions will not be exchanged between us and non-affiliated companies.

If we do share personal information with a non-affiliated company, to the extent practical, we require

that they protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. We cannot, however,

guarantee how these non-affiliated companies will use your personal information.

 **Personal Information Gathered Under Previous Versions of This Privacy Policy.**

Personal information collected via the Site will generally be governed by the version of the Privacy Policy

in effect at the time the information was gathered. We will not retroactively make material changes to the

way we use personally identifiable information collected under previous versions of this Privacy Policy

without obtaining your consent.

 **Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information.**

We sometimes use the non-personal information that we collect to improve the design and content of the

Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet

experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how the Site is used, as well as to

offer you products, programs or services.

Sometimes we share aggregate information with others, including Affiliates and non-affiliated companies.

 **Receipt of Communications; Opt-Out.**

If you would prefer not to receive marketing or promotional e-mails from us that may relate, for example,

to new services or offerings, you may opt-out of receiving these communications using the opt-out

mechanism that is contained in an email.

Following your opt-out, please be aware that we, or our Affiliates, may continue to contact you via email or

postal mail for administrative or informational purposes, including, but not limited to, follow-up messages

regarding the administration of your account, any services, features or functions you have affirmatively

enrolled in or registered to use, any promotions or sweepstakes you have participated in or have entered,

goods, services or products you have ordered or other transactions you have undertaken on the Site.

 **Collection of Information By Others.**

The Site may contain links to other websites, including links that are placed there by us, such as third-party

advertisements or text hyperlinks. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices

of any other website. We encourage all users of the Site to be aware of when they leave the Site, and

to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy

policy applies solely to information collected by the Site, through the Site. We may offer additional e-mail

services or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with non-affiliated companies. Based on

our agreement with them, these third parties may obtain personal information that site visitors voluntarily

submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. We have no control over the use of this

information by these companies.

 **Online Tracking and Advertising.**

We collect information regarding the Site visitors through various technologies, such as cookies, Flash

cookies and Web beacons, including when you visit our sites and applications or use our applications on

third-party sites or platforms.

 **Clickstream Data.**

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information,

which is sometimes referred to as "Clickstream Data," can be collected and stored by a web site's server.

Clickstream Data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the

web site from which you linked to the Site. We may use Clickstream Data as a form of non-personal

information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of the Site, how visitors

navigate throughout the Site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors.

This information will only be used to improve the Site. Any collection or use of Clickstream Data will be

anonymous and aggregate.

 **Supplementing Information.**

From time to time we may supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such

as information validating your address. Thus, information we obtain through the Site may be intermingled

with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than the Site, including both

offline and online sources.

 **Discussions and Community Tools.**

We may, from time to time, make review lists, chat rooms, forums, message boards, blogs, newsgroups and

other community tools available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these

areas becomes public information for other users to view and for us to use. For example, from time to time,

we may use the content you write (including your name or screen name if you post it) for promotional

purposes, in e-mail newsletters or elsewhere, and by using the Site and/or these chat rooms, forums,

message boards, news groups, and other community tools, you agree that we may do so. You should

exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone – not just

us – may access your publicly posted information.

 **Our Commitment to Security.**

We believe we have in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard

and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect

online. Whenever personal information is passed on to non-affiliated companies, to the extent practical, we

require that they also have in place the appropriate safeguards. We cannot, however, guarantee that they do

so.

 **Notice to California-Based Users.**

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, if you are a resident of California, you may make a written

request to the Site about how we have shared your personal information during the prior calendar year with

third parties for their direct marketing purposes. In response to your written request, under California Civil

Code Section 1793.83(c)(2), the Site is allowed to instead provide you with a cost-free means to opt-out of

such sharing, or a "Customer Choice Notice".

The Site has chosen to provide you with a cost-free means to opt-out of such sharing. If you would like to

exercise your rights under California law, please send your written request to the email address or postal

address below, or call us at telephone number below. Within 30 days of receiving your request, the Site will

provide you with a Customer Choice Notice.

EPICTIMES INC

E-MAIL: privacy@epictimes.com

The California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014)

provides that California residents are entitled to know how the Site responds to "Do Not Track" browser

settings. The Site does not currently take action to respond to Do Not Track signals, as a uniform

technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and reserve

the right to adopt a standard once one is created.

 **International Users.**

If you are visiting the Site from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through

and to servers located in the United States and all information you provide will be processed and securely

maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. IN ADDITION,

IF YOU ARE LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES, YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR

INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH

MAY BE DEEMED BY OTHER COUNTRIES TO HAVE INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION (see,

for example, European Union Directive 95/46/EC of 24 October 1995, a copy of which can be found

[here](http://www.epictimes.com/privacy-policy/)). Users of the Site located in countries outside of the United States of America who submit personal

information do thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy

and to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the information in the United States of America.

This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of Delaware and the United States

of America, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the United

States of American in the State of Delaware.

 **How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information.**

For instructions on how you can access the personal information that we have collected about you online,

or how to correct any errors in such information, please [contact us](http://www.epictimes.com/contact/).

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before

granting access or making corrections.

 **Special Note for Parents.**

We will not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under 13 years old in violation of

applicable law. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to the Site without your

permission, please contact us. We have taken commercially reasonable steps to restrict use of the Site to

those who are at least 13 years old. We do not market products or services for purchase by

children and all children's products or services we market are for purchase by adults only, or with adult

permission.

 **Transfer of Business Assets.**

The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among

transferred assets if the Site, we, or parent(s) or any or all of Affiliates or any of our assets are ever

acquired by a third party.

 **Changes to this Policy.**

Because our business needs may change over time, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change,

modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use

your personal information in a way that differs from this policy, we will revise this policy as appropriate.

Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such

changes. This policy is effective as of 01/08/2014.

 **How to Contact Us.**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may [contact us](http://www.epictimes.com/contact/).
